<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rofiqul's Portfolio</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Rofiqul's Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 12:13:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Log Parser &amp; Business Process Extraction</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/logparser/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 12:13:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/logparser/</guid><description/></item><item><title>FBEYE</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/fbeye/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2020 18:19:35 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/fbeye/</guid><description/></item><item><title>OMS (Ontology Management System)</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/oms/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/oms/</guid><description/></item><item><title>QUIC Protocol</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/quic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 18:07:16 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/quic/</guid><description/></item><item><title>High Security Driving License of Bangladesh (HSDL)</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/hsdl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jul 2019 18:19:35 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/hsdl/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Optimal Execution of Virtualized Network Functions for Applications in Cyber-Physical-Social-Systems - IEEE Access</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/blog/ieee_acess/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/blog/ieee_acess/</guid><description>Cyber-physical-social systems exploit the relationship between humans, computers, and the physical environment to provide high-quality real-time and personalized services. Provisioning services for applications in networks of large datacenters (DCs) is carried out as service function chaining (SFC) by linking ordered list of functions. With the development of software, defined networks and network function virtualization, SFC has gained more attention in the industry for deploying larger applications. Provisioning different service functions (SFs) of an SFC in different DC in a multi DC environment is a challenging task.</description></item><item><title>Optimal execution of virtualized network functions in a multi-data-center cloud - IEEE Region 10 Humanitarian Technology Conference (R10-HTC)</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/blog/r10htc/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2017 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/blog/r10htc/</guid><description>Provisioning services for applications in networks of large data-centers is carried out as service function chaining (SFC) by linking ordered list of functions. With the development of software defined network (SDN) and network function virtualization (NFV), SFC has gained more attention in the industry for deploying larger applications. Provisioning different virtualized functions (VFs) of an SFC in different data-centers in a multi data-center environment is a challenging task. Existing works on serving SFC select a service function path (SFC) along which the VFs are executed.</description></item><item><title>National Energy Hackathon</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/blog/neh/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:49:27 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/blog/neh/</guid><description>Honorable Prime Minister of Bangladesh’s dream initiative of establishing Digital Bangladesh flourishes few steps ahead as the Ministry of power energy and Mineral Resource proudly announces National Power and Energy Week 2017. It is one of the biggest events of the year where the nation’s biggest revolutionary advances in the power and energy sector will be showcased along with weeklong engaging events.
Participated with four team members and Won 10th place among over 75+ teams.</description></item><item><title>Virtual-Shelf</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/virtualshelf/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2017 18:19:35 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/portfolio/virtualshelf/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Smart City Hachathon</title><link>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/blog/smartcity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 13:06:26 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://rofiqul-islam.github.io/blog/smartcity/</guid><description>Dhaka, one of the world’s megacities , is also among the list of least livable cities. Overcoming Dhaka’s problems calls for disruptive thinkers and innovators to find solutions with the help of Information and communication technology. The main purpose of the Hackathon was to come up with implementable digital solutions to reduce the impact of the problems faced daily in city life. As Grameen Phone constantly learns, evolves and improves on its digital journey, it takes in some of its best learning opportunities from the community.</description></item></channel></rss>